(Raj:)I say you tell Alex your heart
belongs to Penny.
(Raj:)I provide her a shoulder to cry on,
then roughly half a year later...
(Raj:)...I give it to her good.
(Sheldon:)I want to thank you all for coming on such
short notice. In the past...
(Sheldon:)...I've reached out to each of you
individually...
(Sheldon:)...but I believe my present situation
requires the collective wisdom of the group.
(Sheldon:)Which, as you can see from
your commemorative t-shirts, I've dubbed...
(Sheldon:)...Sheldon Cooper's Council of Ladies.
(Penny:)What is happening?
(Sheldon:)I need your advice about a delicate
workplace situation.
(Sheldon:)To protect those involved,
I'll be changing their names.
(Bernadette:)Who's involved?
(Sheldon:)A short, bespectacled colleague of mine...
(Sheldon:)...who lives in the shadow
of his brilliant roommate.
Uh... Let's call this colleague
Ricardo Shilly-Shally.